topworldnet.blogspot.in 2017-12-20

# Privacy Policy

As the result of your access and use of website, you hereby agree to the term of this privacy  policy. If you are not agree with our privacy policy we advice you and request you not to access the website. We reserve the right to revise our terms of privacy policy time to time. Your continue access to the website will indicate your acceptance of any changes in our privacy policy.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**  
Non personal information collected by www.topworldnet.blogspot.com from its visitor are :

Internet Protocol (IP) Address

Online Presence

Activity Type On Wbsite

Browser type or domain name of visitor

The viewing pattern of visitor collectoed by Google Analytics..  
Website may disclose the non personal information (mentioning above) to its marketing partner and advertiser so that these third party may learn the requirements of our user and can improve it.

Note : Your IP address will not be shared with any one and can not be disclosed with any third party.

**Google Adsense**  
Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>
